RUPAK ACHARYA

Kathmandu, Nepal · acharyarupak391@gmail.com

https://rupakacharya.com.np/ · https://www.linkedin.com/in/acharyarupak391

I am an enthusiastic and keen learner in the field of computers, programming and current technological issues. I have been involved in programming for more than 4 years now and currently involved as a Professional Full Stack Developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022-01-01 - Present

FRONTEND ENGINEER, NEPTUNE MUTUAL

Working on web3 & blockchain with React & other modern tech stacks

2021-09-01 - 2022-01-01

FULL STACK DEVELOPER, INFINITY DIGITAL AGENCY(IDA)

Working on dynamic React apps w/ Server SideRendering(SSR) using NextJS, backend with NodeJS and using other tools such as tailwind-css, headless-ui

2021-12-01 - 2022-03-10

REACT DEVELOPER, KARYATHALO [Part-time]

Working on dynamic React dashboard app w/ Redux, axios & various other libraries

2020-12-01 - 2021-09-01

JAVASCRIPT & REACTJS DEVELOPER, BERRYBYTES

Working on dynamic website development using ReactJS with tools like Axios, Redux, MUI

TRAINING

2019-02-18 - 2019-02-23

MACHINE LEARNING WITH PYTHON, MICROSOFT

Basic Machine Learning Training using python Familiarity with Scikit-learn, pandas, numpy etc. packages

2018-05-20 - 2018-05-29

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Course on HTML, CSS and JavaScript for creating dynamic and responsive web sites

EDUCATION

AUG 2016 - AUG 2020

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY (B. TECH), MALLA REDDY COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY (MRCET), **HYDERABAD, INDIA**

Graduated with a bachelor's degree in **Computer Science & Engineering**.

APR 2012 - APR 2016

INTERMEDIATE DEGREE, KALIKA HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL, KALIKANAGAR, BUTWAL

Achieved the Intermediate Degree by obtaining the GPA of 7.3

JAN 2012

SLC, AXIS INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL, SUKHANAGAR, BUTWAL

Got School Leaving Certificate (SLC) with 81%

SKILLS

- Web Dev [Fullstack]
- JS (Vanilla, ReactJS, NextJS)
- Typescript
- Python
- DB: Postgres, MongoDB
- Git
- Golang
- HTML, CSS

- Blockchain & Web3
- AWS (basic)
- MUI, tailwindcss, styled-components
- Object-Oriented Programming
- Machine Learning
- Tensorflow with Keras

CERTIFICATES & LICENSES

ISSUED: June, 2019

MACHINE LEARNING WITH PYTHON, MICROSOFT

Basic Machine Learning Training using python

Familiarity with Scikit-learn, pandas, numpy etc. packages

ISSUED: May, 2020

INTRODUCTION TO TENSORFLOW IN PYTHON, DATACAMP

Using Tensorflow and Keras, to run various Machine Learning models

Working with various datasets like MNIST

CONCLUSION

I have always been eager and passionate about programming, web development, machine learning and always excited to be a part of something that would directly or indirectly affect the world to be a better place through the means of programming.